Yes
Worst.
They hear it and come right up.
It's really bad.
That was fast.
I'm impressed
Oh, my God!
Just a little bit.
Yuna-san...
Yuna-san was sleeping a little.
She was sleeping a little
This is amazing.
It's not a regular thing, but...
Hello.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
So...
It's pouring.
I'm filming in the pouring rain.
Wow, that's great.
Yes, it is.
It's really pouring.
We're actually supposed to be doing something different today.
That's right.
We were going to do a really great project.
Yeah, it was super fun.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It was perfect, you know, me too.
I was looking forward to it.
And then there was this downpour, so that kind of put a damper on it.
Yes, ma'am.
We'll do it another time.I'll get back to that next time, but for today, on the contrary, it's not such a downpour.
But today, on the contrary, we don't have downpours like this.
That's for sure.
I'd like to go sightseeing in Matsushima, which can be enjoyed even in a downpour!
Yay!
So I'm in Matsushima today.
Yeah.
Have you been there?
I've been to Matsushima quite a bit.
My family comes here sometimes.
Oh...
With the curry buns...
The curry bun?
That's right.
They have that?
I've never heard of it before.
But it's been a while since I've been here, and it's kind of nice.
Right? Right?
Yes, it is.
Do you have it?
Yes, I have.
I used to come here a lot when I was in high school.
In high school?
Yes, I did.
The winter lights...
It's great!
It's like the leaves are lit up.
It's nice.
So many things.
Yeah.
There are many places to enjoy in Matsushima.There are many places to enjoy in Matsushima.
That's right.
Today, in this rain
I'm going to enjoy Matsushima here in the three prefectures of Japan!
Yay!
I'm not going to let the rain stop me!
Oh!
So the first one is a sightseeing boat!
A cruise ship.
It's my first one.
Me too.
I'm so happy.
I'd like to go on a cruise ship.
Let's go!
Waiting for the cruise ship.
Yes, yes, yes.
I just got a ticket for the green car.
I got a ticket for the green car.
Oh, right...
I didn't know there was such a thing as a green car on a cruise ship.
Yes, they do.
I didn't know that.
I've never taken the green car on the Shinkansen either.
First time on a boat.
I got on the green car on the boat first.
You like this? You like it?
Yeah, I think so.
But will we see it? It's raining on the island.
I'm sure.I'm sure.
Can you see it?
What if we don't see anything?
We'll just be on the boat for 50 minutes.
I'm sure that's not true.
I'm sure there's a good view, even in the rain.
Rainy.
I'm sure it will.
I'm looking forward to it.
I love it. I don't have to take Yu's picture.
I'm kind of getting that shot of him.
It's raining today. It's nasty.
I'll do my best.
Whenever you want, beautiful.
Okay, here we go.
He's sleeping... he's sleeping...
That's the worst.
She'll hear you and get up right away.
That was really bad.
It was so bad.
I really wondered what was going on.
I thought I had to film something.
I have a good visual today.
I was surprised when you came up to me with a straight face.
Surprise.
You're really bad today.
That's funny.
Oh, it's funny.
Highlight of the day.
Really no good
Really, really bad today.Really, no. Today.
It's so bad.
My hair is already done.
Rainy days are really no good
It's no good.
Oh, it's funny.
It's not good to cancel today.
I don't mind if it doesn't stay on.
I'm coming home to be off the air.
That's funny.
It starts at 12:00, so I'll wait.
I'm off.
I wonder which one.
Uh, really.
Eh, wait a minute. Okay, wait a minute.
Hey, stiffy boat.
Yeah, there's a lot of customers, right?
Yeah, there's a lot of people.
Oh, yeah.
I'll turn it over.
Maybe more tourists.
Yeah, I guess.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Well, that'll be fun.
What, no lightning? This is...
I know, right? Oh, my gosh.
What? It's really thundering.
No, it's not.
Oh, no.Oh, no.
No, no, no, it's the sound of an engine.
I thought it was thunder.
Which one is it? The engine?
The engine. What the hell?
I thought it was gonna be thunder.
It's just an engine.
I'm so scared.
I think it's lightning. It's raining like crazy.
Oh, that's funny.
It's amazing.
It's like a big, everyday thing.
Indeed.
You have to have an opportunity like this, don't you?
Yeah, and it's raining.
Yeah.
Amazing.
Yay.
It's the ocean.
Yay!
Let's go around.
So, yes
To the pleasure boat
We've arrived!
Wow!
It's even better than I imagined!
It's so magnificent!
There was also coffee.
It looks like adults can drink it.Adults seem to be able to drink.
There's some snacks.
Isn't it amazing? So it's really something.
Yeah, it is.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you very much.
It's fun to be an adult.
This is fun.
Yes, it is.
Looking at the view
Looking at the view.
Not an adult?
I'm not an adult.
The way you read it.
I love it.
It's a dream come true.
It's a dream.
This is a dream.
It's his dream for when he grows up.
So far, it's just cherry-blossom viewing.
He says that's great.
I'm so happy.
That's great.
Someone's coming out.
Oh, my God, it's coming out.
It's coming out.
Oh, my God.
What if he doesn't come out?If they don't show up...
Which one are we?
Yeah, we are.
It's hot.
Oh, man.
We're the only ones who get it.
Love and love
That's love and that's love
Taiko Dae
Oh, no!
No one can understand it
Fumi Sayo
I'm going to sing an old song.
That's great!
That's great
Oh, my God.
That's so great.
That's great.
Thank you for watching!
JR East E233 Series
Yohujima is inujima
Thank God!
It was great!
It was fun even in the rain!
It was comfortable.
It looks like they are going to have dinner.
Oh, yeah.Oh yeah.
Yeah!
Are you happy?
I am happy.
I haven't eaten anything since this morning.
Azuki is happy.
He's happy.
He's happy when there's food.
That's good. What do you want to eat?
But it's the Matsushima Sea,
Of course.
Something nautical.
Yes, that's right. If it's this close to the sea,
That's right. It's like diving and eating.
That's about the level of it.
That's nice. I want to dive down and eat it.
That would be fun.
What's it famous for?
I don't know.
I know there are a lot of fashionable cafes,
There are some famous ones.
I have an image of it.
Pudding, for example.
That's right. I know it's famous.
I know, but I've never eaten rice properly.
That's true.
I enjoy eating and walking around,
I know that kind of thing,
I guess so.
I don't have a big meal.
I'm looking forward to it.Looking forward to it.
I want to try it. I'd like to try something like that.
That's nice.
It's nice. Only on a rainy day.
Yes, it is.
And the sound of thunder.
Thunder.
I thought it was thunder,
But I don't think it's thunder. If it was raining like this and sounded like this.
I'd think it was thunder.
I do. I do.
It's interesting.
I wonder what it is.
It's thunder.
It's thunder. What is this, everyone?
Please be careful.
It seems that thunderstorms occur quite often when it comes to Matsuma.
I felt like I was being called "Mr. Northeast" by Rin-nari.
It's as if you know me.
Yes, I do.
But you can't just say, "Oh, you know..." just by taking a quick look.
You can't say, "Oh, it's Mr. Touhoku.
It's more like, "I've heard of you before," when you see your name written on the back.
That's right. I know them, too.
But I'm still happy.
Just because you know me.
There are places like Tsurimori.There are things like the Tsurimori forest.
It's true.
A huge fishing forest.
Amazing. There are so many things here.
This area.
Even Miyagi people can enjoy it.
It's definitely fun.
You mean Matsushima is good?
They have beef tongue, too.
That's true.
Sounds delicious.
I want some beef tongue.
It's so cute.
Dumplings.
They look really good.
This and the Insta-evidence.
Beef tongue curry bun.
Looks absolutely delicious.
As expected, some of the kids look like they're on some kind of school trip.
If you get mixed up with them....
By all means.
I'd be happy to do it.
I'll do anything.
But, you know, if you like school trips,
You know, you could take a tour when you go sightseeing.
Too much fun. Too much fun.
Too much fun.
Let's go there soon!
Let's go!
Think about Tordakah and other things here.I'm thinking of Tordaka and others here.
I don't think anyone eats the best.
I know.
For Tordaka.
Right.
I don't know if it's good.
Okay, I'll take this one, please.
Please.
Oh, okay.
Excuse me, please.
Do you think I'll be in it?
You'll be in it? With me.
No, thank you.
I'm so happy.
You're welcome to try it.
Hey, good sir.
Superb seafood!
Chi-ashi-don!
Amazing!
It's amazing, isn't it?
Bon appétit!
Yuck!
Oh, yeah.
Let's start with the Toro.
That's good.
Toro first.
I'll start with Toro.
I'll go with...
I'll start with sea urchin.
I'll start with the sea urchin.I'll start with the sea urchin.
Oh, that's good.
Crikey!
Bon appétit!
Ha-ha-ha-ha, you're so sweet!
Oh, my God, it's so good!
Yummy? Tasty?
Soft?
Fat.
Fat!
Tuna is so delicious!
I'm impressed.
A little bit.
Yuna-san said a little
This is amazing
Not this one, though
Bon appétit!
Delicious.
Oh, here it is. It's gone up a little bit.
A little bit.
It's so delicious!
Mellow
I've never eaten it like this.
It's so thick!
I don't know, it's so thick.
Delicious!
It feels so fresh.
I know, right?
I'm sure it's all delicious.
If they took everything at this quality, I wouldn't be able to stop myself.If they took all of this quality, it would be a little hard to stop.
You're right.
I have to be impressed every time.
It's amazing.
Yuuna-san...
Today...
The rainbow didn't look good.
How long are you going to keep saying that?
Oh, my God.
Ms. Yuna.
Here.
Thank you. It's fine.
I don't mind.
You're the one who has shown your face in the past.
Bon appétit.
Yeah!
Yes! Yes! It's delicious!
Wow!
Good!
Two!
It's so good!
Hey!
Oh, my God.
You know, sea urchins, they're so fresh.
It's so fresh.
Right!
Delicious!
You'll be surprised.
I've never eaten anything like it.
It's so good!
If it were really private...If it was a real private
I'd eat more and more and more and more without stopping.
I'd want to keep going and going and going and going!
Time to go through from the area too!
Wow!
This is delicious!
The wasabi is definitely spicy!
Oh, my gosh!
Bon appétit!
Good night.
It's good, isn't it?
It's like fat, isn't it?
I've never had melt-in-your-mouth mange before.
I heard it's all new to you today.
Delicious.
It's good, isn't it?
Sweet.
It's got a nice fatty taste
And ikura-don (salmon roe on rice)
Mouthwatering!
I'm so happy!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
I got a GoPro today.
Is that what this is?
It's delicious!
I'd like to go there in private.
I'd love to.
Matsushima is amazing!
This is great!
It's new for my family!New to the family.
Yes, I know.
There was a concert at Miyake.
The next day or something.
I'm sure everyone who's staying here
You should come to Matsushima!
Even if it rains, it's still fun.
It's not just Sendai.
I want you to go to other places.
There are so many good places.
There are so many good places that we don't even know about.
Delicious!
Oh, it's so good!
3,600 yen. I feel it.
I feel it.
It's amazing.
Hey.
This is amazing.
I can feel it.
It's too good.
I'm so happy.
I can sleep.
You're sleepy.
You say you're going to sleep.
It's so good!
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious, wasn't it?
I'm so satisfied.
I felt like I tasted everything.
Seafood.Seafood.
It's like...
It's like all the good stuff is gathered together.
It was delicious.
You should try it!
I recommend it.
There are so many things to choose from.
It's true, isn't it?
There are so many different kinds.
I'm going to check out the store tomorrow.
I'm going to go check it out.
I'll be there.
[fast forward]
Hey.
There's everything.
It's true.
The variety is amazing.
Oh, Kinoya!
Oh, really!
Mr. Kinoya.
Kinoya-san!
Looks delicious!
It's so beautiful.
The patterns...
Gorgeous!
Gummi!
Yoo-hoo!
He's squirming.
You're squirming.He's squirming.
This girl's not a snapper.
He's doing so much.
Oh, I'm scared.
You scared me.
That scared me.
Oh, no.
I'm scared.
You scared the shit out of me, ladies and gentlemen.
There were so many of them in this aisle.
Oh, my God.
I thought she was the only one.
But there were so many.
I wonder why they don't go in there.
They're so cute.
I wonder if they want to go in.
Oh, they're trying to get in.
Let's go in.
Oh, they're in.
What? It's so small.
I'm in.
You can do it from the other side.
Yes, you can.
So, here we go.
At Matsushima Fish Market
I had a delicious seafood bowl!
It was so good!
Thank you for the food!Thank you for the food.
Good night.
Come on, it's okay.
I had a delicious seafood bowl.
Next time...
I'd like to visit Yukitakeya!
Yay!
Famous rice crackers...
And a café?
I see...
It seems like they have a lot of things to offer.
I'd like to go there.
Let's go!
We've arrived at Yukitake-ya!
We're here!
Amazing!
There are so many rice crackers!
There are so many!
Wow, wow, wow!
It smells so good!
I think we have rice crackers here, big rice crackers.
I'm going to have some of those.
Bon appétit!
Oh, the crackers!
Amazing!
Zarame, wet crackers.
I'm curious about it.
It's not wet rice crackers.
Oh, no.
Wet crackers are made by a special process. They're crunchy, crunchy, crunchy.Your wet rice crackers are crunchy, crunchy, crunchy, crunchy, crunchy, crunchy, crunchy, crunchy, crunchy, crunchy, crunchy, crunchy, crunchy, crunchy, crunchy.
I love your wet rice crackers.
I haven't tasted them in a long time. That's true.
That's true.
Can I have a sample of this? No, it's okay.
Oh my God, I haven't tasted anything like this in years.
You haven't, have you? No.
I'll have a jarame. I'll have a jarame. I'm impressed.
I'm back. I'm back. I'm back.
I recommend this one.
Bon appétit.
Is it good?
Is it sweet?
Sweet.
It's sweet.
It's so crunchy.
It's so chewy.
It's amazing.
A piece of cake
Wet Kari?
Yes, wet kari!
Bon appétit!
Yum!
It has a flavor...
It's when the flavor develops.
But the texture is crunchy.
It's really just the right place
When it's on
I think this is where it was made.
I'm going to go
I'm now matching the freshly baked tapeI am now matching the freshly baked tapes!
Wow! Wow!
Wow!
Wow! Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my gosh!
There's so much steam.
That's amazing.
Please be careful when you eat it, it's really hot!
It's really hot, so please be careful.
Thank you very much.
Here you go.
Hot.
Really hot.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the rice crackers.
It's freshly baked.
Is it hot? It's really hot.
And freshly dipped in soy sauce.
It smells so good.
Every time you put it on, you put it on.
Yeah, it's a food technique.
I ate it.
Bon appétit!
We can nibble together.
Mmm! Yum! Delicious!
Delicious!
The soy sauce taste is good.
Yeah, it's like...Yeah, it's so good!
Warm rice crackers are so delicious!
It's not so easy to find.
It's not easy to find.
Warm rice crackers.
Mmmm...
I had a lot of fun in the city today.
That was fun.
I felt hopeless.
It was fun.
I was looking forward to the maiko project,
But it ended up raining.
It was raining, but I had a great time,
It was a very happy day.
Riding on the telemonkey.
Your hair looks so mature.
I did indeed. Sober.
Elegant.
It was great.
I learned something new about Tohoku,
It was a great day.
Like the day after Touhoku's concert,
It's really a wonderful place.
I know. Something to calm the adrenaline.
Surely.
To calm down the afterglow of the concert.
It's a great way to end a memorable day.
So, this time, even on a rainy day, you can have fun,
I can enjoy it with all my might, and I'm looking forward to seeing you all again.It was an all-out enjoyable Matsushima outfit.
I hope you will all come too.
Bye bye!
Thank you.